コードギアス反逆のルルーシュR2 TURN 16　超合集国決議第壱號
TURN 16　超合集国決議第壱號
The world is moving, thanks to
the miracles Zero has performed.
世界は動き行くゼロが起こした奇跡によって
The world is being reborn, thanks
to the actions Zero has taken.
世界は生まれ行くゼロが示した行動によって
Yes...The world is moving
to the next stage it should.
そう 今世界は 次のありかたにすすもうとしている
Along with many desires and heaving
emotions, Zero must carry on.
あまたな欲と感情のうねりとともに
ゼロはすすまねばならない
時を刻む針を　とめないためにも
Because the hands which mark
out time can not be stopped.
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
Kireigoto dake jaa ikirenai
Pretty words alone won't sustain you
Yasashisa dake jaa iyasenai
Kindness alone won't heal you
Ubawareta nowa nanda
What is it that was stolen from you
Kawaranai sekai de
In this unchanging world
Kikoetekita nowa nanda
What is it that you hear
Shikisai no uta
A song of color
Everything is bright...
Kudakechitta yume wo
Let our crumbled dreams resound
Asu no hate ni hibikaseru you ni
At the edge of tomorrow
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Bokura hitotsu ni
Becomes one with us
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
UNITED FEDERATION OF NATIONS
RESOLUTION NUMBER ONE
皇帝陛下が？
The emperor!
行方不明？
He's disappeared?!
はい先ほど シュナイゼル宰相閣下より連絡をいただきました
Yes. I've just received word
from Prime Minister Schneizel.
当面はここにいる人たちだけの話とさせてください
It's imperative that we restrict this
news to only those present here.
帝国本土でも ごく一部のだけしか知らされていないようですから
Apparently, this news has been reported to
only a handful of people in the homeland.
何があったというのですか？
What are you saying has happened?!
今は 調査中ということで
He says they're still investigating that now.
おまちください
Wait, please! What happens to our
preparations to attack the Chinese Federation?
中華連邦への攻撃準備は どうなさるのですか
皇帝陛下が宣戦布告をされねば こちらからは手がだせません
If His Majesty can't issue a declaration of war,
then we can't do anything!
治安の問題もあります
There are questions of
domestic security as well.
こんなことがナンバーズどもに知られたらことですから
We have to decide on a policy to
take if the Numbers learn about this!
方針をきめていただかねば
それは
Well...
総督はナナリー様です
You are the viceroy, Princess Nunnally.
Miss Lohmeyer, aren't you placing too
much responsibility on Her Highness?
ミス ローマイヤそれは責任のおしつけですか？
I...I meant no disrespect...
いえ そんなことは
喜んでいいのか？陛下がおられないということは
Should I be happy about this?
The emperor's disappearance means
Nunnally is safe for now, but...
ナナリーの命は助かると言う意味だけど
やったブリタニアのこの動きは皇帝が不在だということ
I've done it! The actions Britannia is
taking means the emperor is absent!
あのとき 向こうの世界におきざりになったようだな
It looks like he was
trapped in that otherworld.
あいつが言っていたことは気になるが
I admit I'm concerned
about what he said before,
今はナナリーの安全を喜ぶべきか
but for now I should be
happy that Nunnally is safe.
あの 私は何をすれば
Um...What should I do?
Let's see...Wear your clothes inside out
and dance on one foot while singing.
そうだな服を裏返しにして
歌いながら片足で踊ってもらおうか
Yes, master.
はいご主人さま
よせ！冗談だ！
Stop it! I was just kidding!
きゃ！ごめんなさい！だからひどいことしないで
I'm sorry!
Please don't beat me!
完全に戻っている
She's completely reverted.
ギアスにかかる前の奴隷の少女に
To the slave girl she once was
before being affected by Geass.
安心しろ俺は君にひどいことはしないよ
Don't worry.
I won't harm you in any way.
約束する本当だ
I promise. It's the truth.
ルルーシュ様
Lord Lelouch.
ジェレミアかどうした？
Jeremiah? What is it?
そうか サザーランドのコクピットにいれて
I see. You hid her inside
the Sutherland's cockpit.
お許しください ルルーシュ様
Please forgive me, Lord Lelouch.
ご命令はせん滅とのことでしたが
You ordered me to destroy them, but killing a
member of the Britannian royal family was just...
ブリタニア皇族を手にかけることは
Forget it.
Rather, I should say well done.
よい いや むしろよくやってくれた
ルルーシュ
Lelouch...What is it you seek
with that accursed power?
お前はその呪われた力で何を求める？
Sister...All I wish to do
is save my little sister.
姉上俺はただ妹を助けたいだけなんです
何を今さら
You dare to say that!
木下
Kinoshita.
A-Asahina...
朝比奈さん
それ 血のあとですよね
Those are bloodstains, aren't they?
What exactly was Zero's operation?
なんだったんです？ゼロの作戦って
It was...
それは
We won't say.
それはいえませんゼロの命令です
Those are Zero's orders.
And it's not just for you.
あなただけではありません
藤堂将軍にも極秘の任務です
This was kept top secret even
from Gen. Tohdoh, as well.
新参者がずいぶんとえらそうじゃない
You're acting awfully important
for a newbie, aren't you?
黒の騎士団における個人の価値はどれだけゼロの信頼を得ているかできまります
The value of an individual in the
Black Knights is determined...
by how much confidence
they earn from Zero.
That's not how I value them.
僕の価値観とはちがうね
すまなかった
I'm sorry!
何言ってんだ！
What the hell are you saying?!
やっていいことと 悪いことがあるだろう！
Some things you just don't do!
いい人ぶって 勝手におしまい？
You think you can just act like a good
guy and then stop when it suits you?!
Well, I'm pissed off about it, so quit trying
to get a free show from Kallen Kouzuki!
収まらないんだよ！
紅月カレンを 安くみるな！
抵抗しないところが ほんと腹たつ！
Not resisting is just
pissing me off more!
さあ 私を殺しなさいよ
Go ahead. Kill me.
捕虜がナイトオブラウンズに手を出したんだから覚悟はしてる
A prisoner just assaulted a Knight of the Round.
I'm ready to die.
まさかいけなかったのは僕だから
I wouldn't, because I was
the one who did wrong!
あんたなんか 大っきらい！
You...I despise you!
そうだこの合集国憲章を批准することで
Yes! By ratifying this united states charter,
it will give birth to a gigantic alliance of nations
that will rival the Holy Britannian Empire!
神聖ブリタニア帝国に匹敵する
巨大な連合国家が誕生する
And its name shall be the
United Federation of Nations!
その名も 超合集国
おお～！
すてきですわ
It's wonderful, Master Zero!
ブリタニアの植民エリアとなった亡命政権からも
The governments-in-exile of the Britannian colonial
areas have already given approval to participate.
参加表明がとどいています
これでわれわれは
With this, we've earned a just
cause to launch a war of liberation!
解放戦争という大義名分を得ました
A just war, huh?
正義の戦争か
きたるべき日本奪還作戦において
If the forthcoming operation to
recapture Japan is successful,
我らが勝利をおさめれば
いまだ様子見をしている勢力も連鎖的に寝返ってくるとシンクー
The other powers who are still unable to
decide will turn to our side in a chain reaction!
うん
しかしそのためには ブリタニアが動く前に超合集国をつくりあげねばならない
But for that, we must form the
U.F.N. before Britannia can act!
時間が勝敗を決する
Time will decide victory or defeat here.
各国を代表する諸君らにも言い分はあるだろうが
All of you here representing your
countries have things you wish to discuss,
but I ask that you cooperate from the
broader viewpoint of the main objective.
ここは大局的見地に立った協力をおねがいしたい
This is all to decide the course of world history!
すべては 世界の趨勢に決着をつけるために！
みなさ～ん こんにちは
Hello there, everyone!
ごめんなさい！
I'm sorry!
新進気鋭のひとりお祭り娘　ミレイ アッシュフォードで～す
It's Milly Ashford, the up-and-coming
one-woman festival, here!
自分で言うなよ
You shouldn't just declare yourself that.
ふふっでは本日のトピックス
Okay, on to today's topics!
なんと駅前が突然動物園に
Now, watch us turn the front of a station into a zoo!
現在池袋駅にて人々を驚かせているのが動物のアートです
Right now, the people heading into Ikebukuro
station are being surprised with Animal Art!
食事を持ってきたんだが
I brought you some food.
It's me.
俺だよ
これはピザっていうんだよ
This is called pizza.
You're hungry, aren't you?
おなかすいただろう
おまえに上げようとおもって　杉山に用意させたんだけど
I wanted to give you some,
so I had Sugiyama make it.
おぼえていないのか
Don't you remember?
ほら おまえも
Here. You have some, too.
いいんだよ 食べて
It's all right. Eat.
はい
Yes, master!
おいしいか？
Is it good?
Yes! Really, really good!
はいすごくすごく
Really. I'm glad.
そうかそれはよかった
会長キャラの作り方をまちがえているんじゃ
Oh, Prez...You're doing your
character establishment all wrong.
ああ そうかこういうのも知らないんだよな
Oh. That's right. You don't know what this is, do you?
悩み事？
Trouble on your mind?
悩んでばかりだ
Nothing but trouble. Even though
I chose this life eight years ago.
8年前に　自分の生き方をきめたはずなのに
信じてるの？8年前の自分なんて
Do you believe in him? The
person you were eight years ago?
過去の決意なんて 愚かだっていいたいのかい？
Are you trying to tell me that my
past decisions were foolish ones?
人の記憶なんてあいまいなもの
Peoples' memories are vague.
There's no point in believing in them.
信じる程の価値はない
そんなことはないよ
That's not true.
There's no point.
価値はない9年前 私が書いた日記がある
I kept a diary nine years ago.
でも私にはこの記憶がない
But I don't remember any of it.
えっ
他にもいっぱい
There's so much more than that.
私の記憶と データとしての記録が違っているの
Differences between the memories
and the data I've been recording.
まさか皇帝陛下のギアス？なぜアーニャに？
Is it possible? The emperor's Geass?
But why use it on Anya?
それだけじゃない
Not just that. Even now,
my memories differ from the data.
今でも記憶がずれることがある
中華連邦で戦った時も いきなり
Even when we were fighting in the
Chinese Federation, they just suddenly...
必要なものとはなんだ？
Tell me, traitorous Sir Kururugi.
What do you need?
裏切りの枢木卿
それは命だ
That would be life.
白ロシア戦線以来ですねブラッドリー卿
I see you're back from the White
Russian front, Sir Bradley.
ナイトオブテン
The Knight of Ten.
相変わらず女を落とすのは大得意らしいな
I see you still have great skill at
making the ladies fall for you.
例の虐殺王女様も?
Like the famous massacre princess...
Speak another word and you will
face me in a duel for honor, sir!
それ以上言えば名誉を賭けて決闘を申し込むことになります?
ああ 忘れたのかな？
Oh? Have you forgotten?
私が人殺しの天才だってことを
I happen to be a genius at killing people.
血筋って～ものを理解できぬナンバーズ上がりが?
Does a Number who can't grasp the
importance of bloodline think he can...
これは ギャラハット
This is...The Galahad!
Don't fight amongst yourselves, you two!
ふたりとも 相手を間違えるな！
ナイトオブワンが
The Knight of One! But why would
Lord Waldstein be here, too?
アルトシュタイン卿までどうしてここに？
愚問だな アーニャ
A foolish question, Anya.
黒の騎士団が攻め込むとしたらこのエリアしかない
This is the only Area the Black
Knights will come to attack. Luciano!
ルキアーノヴァルキリエ隊もそのために連れてきたのだ
I brought the Valkyrie squadron
here for that, as well.
ガレスもそのために用意した
The Gareths have also been prepared for that.
Save your grandstanding for the battlefield!
お前のスタンドプレイは戦場で示せ
今はシュナイゼル殿下指揮の下 我らが力を合わせる時?
Now is the time for us to join forces
under the command of Prince Schneizel!
ふん わかってますよ
Understood, my lord. If you say so.
あなたが言われるなら
そうルルーシュがそんなことを
So, Lelouch was like that, huh?
お兄様はいじっぱりなんです
Big brother can be terribly stubborn,
but he's actually very kind.
でも本当はとてもやさしくて
私のお兄ちゃんもそうだった
My big brother was like that, too.
ほぉ～話にはきいていたが こんなお嬢ちゃんが黒の騎士団のエースとはねえ
Oh...I'd heard, but can this lovely young
lady really be the ace of the Black Knights?
ここに入る許可はだしていないはずですが
I don't believe I gave you permission
to come in here, Sir Bradley.
ブラッドリー卿
My apologies, Your Highness.
これは失礼を
So, you're the Vampire of Britannia.
そう あなたがブリタニアの吸血鬼さん
Yes. It's a shame I'd suck your blood
as well, if this was a battlefield.
ああここが戦場ならあんたの血も吸えたのに残念だよ
So? Are you here to bring me back to the homeland?
で 私は本国おくりってことかしら
いや 人質としてしばらくここにいてもらう
No. Please stay here and
play hostage for a bit longer.
人質に必要なものはなんだ？命だ
What is it you need for a hostage? It's life.
As long as they're alive, you
can do anything to their body...
命さえあればその体に何がおころうと
プライドはないんですか？ブラッドリー卿
Have you no pride, Sir Bradley?
武器をもたない女性を相手に
Taking on an unarmed woman?
So naive...The little boy who only
has a good family to boast of.
はは甘いな家柄だけのおぼっちゃんは
家の名前だけで認められるなんて
So, you're saying it's so easy
to become a Knight of the Round...
そんなに軽いのですかナイトオブラウンズは
just through recognition
of your family name?
はあ？ランスロットにフレイヤを？
Mount the F.L.E.I.J.A. on Lancelot?
スザク君には紅蓮をつかってもらうつもりだったんだけど
We were intending to have
Suzaku use the Guren, but...
What? Me?
えっ？僕が？
Sorry, I also got carried away with it.
ごめんなさいね私もついついのっちゃって
ロイドさんといっしょに 気付いたら趣味の世界に
Before we realized, Lloyd and I had
gotten wrapped up in our hobby, so...
Hobby?
趣味？
Having one of Rakshata's machines to
tinker with was too much of a temptation.
ラクシャータのマシンだからいじりやすくって
そしたら誰も乗れないものに
Now it's so souped up, nobody can fly it.
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
We need you as a Devicer again!
デヴァイサーの出番だねえ
Excuse me, Prof. Lloyd?
About the Lancelot...
あの ロイド先生 ランスロットの件ですが
戦術兵器に戦略兵器を乗せる気かい？?
You want to mount a strategic
weapon on a tactical weapon?
それだけの理由はあります
For only one reason.
Because any matter caught within
the primary neutralization field...
一次制圧圏内に含まれた物質は
フレイヤのコラプス効果によって
will be completely annihilated by
the F.L.E.I.J.A. collapse effect.
完全に消滅しますから
待って！そんなものをスザク君にうたせるつもり？
Wait a minute! You want Suzaku
to fire a weapon like that?!
同じ民族を虐殺?
He'd be massacring his own people.
Suzaku, do you still consider yourself an Eleven?
スザク まだイレヴンと同族意識があるの？
I want to entrust F.L.E.I.J.A. to you.
私は　あなたにフレイヤを委ねたい?
僕に 背負えと？?
You'd have me bear this burden?
You were Princess Euphemia's knight, after all.
ユーフェミア様の騎士でしょ あなたは?
あは～ニーナくん
Ah! Nina, my dear.
That contradiction won't just kill Suzaku.
この矛盾はさ スザクくんだけじゃない
It'll kill you, too.
君を殺すよ～?
U.F.N. CHARTER RATIFICATION CEREMONY SITE
はい　全世界にむけての報道準備はおわりました
Right, we've finished preparations
for a worldwide broadcast.
シンクー様や藤堂将軍は控室に
Mr. Xing-ke and General Tohdoh
are in the waiting room. Right.
はい
わかった私はインドとギニア代表にあったあと
Understood. I'll meet you in the assembly hall...
after I meet with the Indian
and Guinean representatives.
会場で合流する
外にはでるなよ
Don't go outside.
Y-Yes, master. And afterward, well...
は はいあと その
What?
なんだ？
いってらっしゃいませ
See you later.
はあ？
いってきます
I'll be off, then.
United States of China Representatives Room
が 合集国憲章の内容については
I...I will leave
the explanation of it...
さ 最高評議会代表　皇神楽耶殿からの説明を
to Representative Kaguya
Sumeragi of the Supreme Council.
はあ
どうしますか？やはり
How are you? If it's too much for you, we can...
いえ！これぐらいは
Oh, no! This much...
できますよ天子様なら
You'll be able to do it, Your Majesty.
Huh?! Good thing we followed Zero, right?!
なあ？ゼロについてきてよかっただろ？
ああ
Right...
そういえば C.C.は？
By the way, where's C.C.?
まだ体調不良だってさ
I heard she's still feeling sick.
お！おめでたとかじゃねえのへへへへ
Morning sickness? Good for her!
Tamaki, maybe you've had a too much to drink.
玉城さん 飲み過ぎでは
You gotta drink to celebrate!
男が化粧というのはどうもな
A man shouldn't have to wear makeup.
晴れの舞台ですから
He does if he wants to look
good for an occasion like this.
あの この戦いが終わったら私
Um, when this battle is over, I...
ん？
と 藤堂鏡志郎にきいてもらいことがあります
There's something I'd like
to tell Kyoshiro Tohdoh.
お やっときたな
Oh! You're finally here!
You think this is the time to be running late?
こんなときに遅刻してる場合か
I know. Sorry.
いや すまない
扇 たいした寝坊だな
Ohgi. This is a record for oversleeping.
逃げた
Got away...
Sorry I'm late. The truth is...
遅れてすみません実は
急ぎましょう
Let's get a move on. This is
a day for the history books.
今日は歴史に残る日ですからね
We're coming to you over Horai Island.
こちらは蓬莱島上空です
合集国憲章　批准の式典が今 まさにはじまろうとしています
The ratification ceremony for the
united states charter is about to begin.
In other words, ratification of
this united states charter...
つまり この合集国憲章を批准することで
我が国に匹敵する巨大な連合国家が誕生する というわけですね
...will create a federation of nations
that will rival our own nation.
分裂したＥＵの一部もはいるとのことですから
As parts of the now broken-up E.U. are joining
as well, it will have great national power.
国力は強大です
ＥＵ脱退国は ポーランド イタリア
Among the former E.U. nations are Poland, Italy...
スザクたちならわかるけど
I can understand about Suzaku and the others,
but why can't I contact Lelouch and Rolo?
なんでロロとルルーシュたちまで連絡がつかないんだよ
これら各国代表をときふせたのは　黒の騎士団なんです
It was the Black Knights who convinced the
representatives of these nations to do this.
ということは 連合の指導者はゼロ
In short, the leader of this union is Zero.
つまり ブリタニアの敵となる可能性が高く
Meaning the probability is high that
it will be an enemy of Britannia.
Right now, our military forces in Kyushu,
Chugoku, and Hokuriku are on alert.
現在 キュウシュウ チュウゴク ホクリクを中心に軍の配備が
As everyone watching this broadcast has seen,
放送をご覧のみなさま ただ今47カ国すべてが 合集国憲章への批准を終えました
all 47 nations have just ratified the
united states charter. Coming up next...
続きまして
Lord Guilford, we've finished preparations
for your review of the troops.
ギルフォード卿閲兵式の準備がととのっておりますので
Right. On my way.
ああ 今むかっている
なんだ？閲兵式の件なら
What? If it's about the troop review...
ギルフォード卿
Lord Guilford.
オ オレンジ君
Orange?
連合国家構想 予想通りね
They're forming a union of nations,
just as we expected.
しかし国ごとに形成された軍隊はどうしても連携を欠く
But the militaries of each country
will never be able to work together.
It'll just be an unruly mob.
烏合の衆でしかありません
No. There's one good option for them.
いや ひとつだけ手はある
...the basic obligations of this
charter shall take precedence.
Finally, article 17 of the united states charter.
最後に 合集国憲章第17条
合集国憲章を批准した国家は　固有の軍事力を永久に放棄する
U.F.N. SUPREME COUNCIL
CHAIRMAN
All ratifying nations to the united states charter...
...do hereby abandon native military power forever.
軍事力の放棄？
Abandon military power?!
Are they mad?!
正気か？
その上で 各合集国の安全については
To guarantee the security of
each member nation instead,
どの国家にも属さない戦闘集団黒の騎士団と契約します
we contract that to the Black Knights,
a fighting force not affiliated with any one country.
契約 受諾した
This contract has been accepted.
We will take funding and personnel from the U.F.N.
我ら黒の騎士団は 超合衆国より資金や人員を提供してもらう
In return, we will become the shield
to defend every member nation...
そのかわり 我らはすべての合集国を守る盾となり
外敵を制する剣となろう
and the sword to oppose any external foe!
Just as I thought.
やはり か
それぞれの国が武力をもつのは騒乱のもと
The source of disturbances in the world is the
possession of military power by disparate nations.
超集衆国では 最高評議会の議決によってのみ
The U.F.N. shall only use military force according
to a resolution by the supreme council.
軍事力を行使します
それでは 私から最初の動議を
And so, I shall put forward our first motion.
The land of the people of
the United States of Japan...
わが合衆国日本の国土は他国により蹂躙され
continues to be held in an unjust
occupation by a foreign power.
不当な占領を受け続けています
黒の騎士団の派遣を要請したいと考えますが
I wish to request that the
Black Knights be dispatched.
賛成の方はご起立を
All those in favor, please rise.
賛成多数よって 超合集国決議　第壱號として
By overwhelming majority, under
U.F.N. resolution number 1,
the Black Knights shall be
dispatched to liberate Japan.
黒の騎士団に日本解放を要請します
Very well! Under U.F.N. resolution number 1,
our first operational objective shall be...
いいでしょう
超合集国決議第壱號
進軍目標は 日本
Japan!
取り戻す我々の日本を！
We're going to retake it! Our Japan!
これでカレンちゃんも
Now we can rescue Kallen, too.
あ ああ そうだな
Uh, yeah. You're right.
ゼロよ
Zero!
What?!
あ 何？！
We've been hacked?!
ハッキングか？
14番のルートからわりこまれて
It's coming in from 14 routes!
皇帝陛下が
Th-The emperor!
お戻りになられた
So, he's back.
偽りの劇場を気取られますか父上
Were you putting on this false theater, Father?
予備ラインを使え！接続を切るんだ
Use the auxiliary lines! Cut the link!
We can't! They've gotten
into the auxiliaries as well!
だめです予備もおさえられています
Zero...You thought
you could get the jump on me?
ゼロよそれでわしをだしぬいたつもりか？
バカな 生きていた？
Impossible! How could he be alive?!
Still, I don't mind.
だが 悪くない
三極のひとつＥＵはすでに死に体
The E.U., which once comprised a
third of the world, is already dead.
つまり貴様の作った小賢しい憲章が
All this annoying charter you've created does...
世界をブリタニアとそうでないものに色分けする
is serve to differentiate Britannia
from the rest of the world on a map.
単純　それゆえに明快
I'm just being simple and clear about this.
After all, whoever succeeds in
this battle shall control the world.
畢竟　この戦いを制した側が
世界を手にいれるということ
So, very well, Zero. Have at me.
いいだろうゼロ
挑んでくるがよい
全てを得るか全てを失うか
Will you win everything or lose everything?
戦いとは元来そういうものだ
That is the essential nature of war.
オール　ハイル　ブリタ～ニア！
ALL HAIL BRITANNIA!
All hail Britannia! All hail Britannia!
オール　ハイル　ブリタニア！
Long live Japan!
日本　万歳！
Long live...
日本！万歳！
JAPAN!
All hail Britannia! All hail Britannia! All hail Britannia!
オール　ハイル　ブリタニア！
日本万歳！日本万歳！日本万歳！
Long live Japan! Long live Japan! Long live Japan!
皇帝が生きていた
The emperor is still alive?!
Um, excuse me. Welcome back.
あの おかえりなさい
This isn't good. I have to rescue
Nunnally at once. At once!
いけない今すぐにナナリーを助けなければ
今すぐに！
I could play the Cornelia card...No.
Hostages would have no effect on him.
コーネリアのカードをこちらに
いや 人質が通じる相手じゃない
Maybe use Rolo and Jeremiah...No, I can't!
ジェレミアとロロを使って
ダメだやつにギアスは通じない
Geass doesn't work on him now! Do I reveal
to the world that Zero is actually Lelouch?
ゼロがルルーシュだと世界中に明かしてしまうか
しかしゼロが敵国の皇子だとなれば
But if I reveal that their leader is an enemy prince,
the Black Knights will fall apart!
黒の騎士団は崩壊する
ナナリーを助けても
Even if I rescue Nunnally, it'll be meaningless
if there's no country that would accept us!
受け入れる国がなければ何の意味もない
Dammit, what do I do?!
くっ どうすればいい？
これ ご主人様のぶん とっておきました
Um, here.
I kept this piece for you, master.
朝ごはん とられていなかったようですから
I don't think you had any breakfast today.
Um, please take it...
あの これ
SHUT UP!
うるさい！
Hey...
ああっ！ごめんなさい！いま綺麗にしますから
Forgive me! I'll clean it up at once!
No, forget that! You're bleeding.
そうじゃない
血がでているじゃないか
What? I'm fine. This happens
to me all the time. I'm fine.
平気です
これくらいいつもより全然平気です
いつもよりって
All the time?
でも 寒い時は助かるんです
It helps when it's cold, though.
ヒリヒリ熱いから
It hurts, but it keeps me warm, at least. It's hard to
move your arms and legs to work when it's cold, so...
寒いと手足が動きにくくて仕事が
だから平気です
So, I'm fine. Better to hurt
on the outside than the inside.
外から痛いほうが 中から痛いよりも
ご主人様 寒いんですか？
Master, are you cold?
ん？ああ そうなのかもしれないな
Hm? Yeah...Maybe that's it.
お前は中から痛いとき どうしていたんだ？
What do you do?
When you hurt inside?
私は 友達
I...
I'd turn to friends...
友達がいたらよかったんですけど
I always wanted a friend.
親とか兄弟と違って友達なら後からでも作れるし
They're not like parents or siblings,
because you can make more later.
でも私にはそんな味方もいなくって
But, I don't really have
anyone on my side like that...
味方
On your side?
あの そう聞いたんですけど 違うんですか？?
Well, that's what I've heard.
Am I wrong?
いや 違わないそれが友達だ?
No, not at all.
That's exactly what a friend is.
はい
Yes?
スザクか
Suzaku?
Lelouch?
ルルーシュ
ああ その ニュース知ってるよな？?
Um, yeah.
Have you seen the news?
Yeah. Now Area 11
will become a battlefield again.
うん これでエリア11はまた戦場になる
トウキョウ租界も危ないかな？?
The Tokyo Settlement will be
in danger again too, won't it?
それは君が決めることだろう？
That depends on what you decide.
え？?
ルルーシュ  君はゼロか？
Lelouch...Are you Zero?
そうだ 俺が ゼロだ?
Yes. I am Zero.
ブリタニアの敵が　僕に何の用だ？
So, what does an enemy of Britannia want with me?
頼む ナナリーを助けてくれ
I'm begging you. Please, save Nunnally!
皇帝は俺を抑えるためにナナリーを人質にしている
The emperor is using Nunnally
as a hostage to pin me down.
だから 俺は隠れて動くしかなかった
That's why I had no choice
but to operate in secret!
頼む スザク
Please, Suzaku! You're the only
person left I can ask this of!
お前以外に頼める人間がいないんだ?
君の頼みなんか　僕が引き受けると思うのか？
You think your requests mean
anything to me at this point?!
思わないそれでもお前しかいないんだ?
No, I don't.
But you're the only one I can ask!
身勝手だな
How selfish.
わかっている
I know. But you're all I have.
All I have!
しかし お前しか お前しか
頼む ナナリーを ナナリーを
Please! Nunnally...Nunnally...
守って下さい
Please, protect her!
わかったただし 条件がある
Very well.
However, on one condition.
ナナリーを守るというのなら
If I protect Nunnally, as you ask, then you must
come to Area 11 by yourself, where she is.
ナナリーがいるこのエリア11に
君が一人で来るべきだ
場所は枢木神社二人っきりで　会おう
The place will be the Kururugi shrine.
The two of us will meet there. Alone.
Dakuse wa oni
This corrupt world is filled with demons
Seigi wa nanzo to
What is justice?
Tou mae ni aragae yo
Resist, don't just question
Akutoku no hana
The flower of evil
Gizen no yume
Dreams of hypocrisy
Mishi me niwa me wo sashi
Give your gaze to the eyes that see them
Sei mo ja mo wakatareru koto nashi
The line between right and wrong cannot be known
Hikari wa tae taiji no you ni
Light is gone, and you slumber
Kimi wa nemuru yami no shikyuu
Like an unborn child in the womb of darkness
Kodoku koso itooshii
Isolation is what you love
Yui-itsu no mikata to naru darou
It will probably be your only ally
Hitori hitori chishio ni mamire
One by one, stained with the tide of blood
Kono jidai ni umare ochita
You were born into this era
Erabareshi oujira yo
Oh, chosen princes
Tatakai koso shukuen
Battle shall be your banquet
Aa ware wa uruwashii zenchi
Oh, I am graceful omniscience
Ai no haha
The loving mother
Kimi wo umu
Who bore you
Kono chichi ni hagukumishi mono wa
The ones who were raised on my breast
Jigoku no harakara
Are your brethren in hell
Mokushi no in
The mark of apocalypse
Shinri wa nanzo to
What is truth
Shirimosezu uzumoreshi intoku no tane
A seed of secrecy buried where no one knows
Moroha no ken
A double-edged sword
Nuku ha niwa ha wo muke
Turn its blade upon the unsheathed blade
Mamorubeki mono dake wo shinjite
Believe only in what you must protect
Aru ga mama ni kimi wa
And in your own way
Kimi wo hanate
You'll set yourself free
こんなことになるなら
強引にでもナナリー救出を前倒しにすべるだったのか
With things like this, should I have
forced my way to save Nunnally sooner?
しかし　それはあまりに危険過ぎる
But as long as Nunnally won't
come to me by her own will,
くっそれとも信じろ
スザクを信じるしかない
I can't help but treat her as a hostage.
俺はスザクを
So long as so many people hate Britannia,
ルルーシュだ
今週も楽しんでくれてありがとう
I can't stop the malice that
will be directed at Nunnally.
いつも応援してくれているみんなにご覧のプレゼントを送る
It would have been too dangerous.
That's right. I'll trust him.
All I can do is trust Suzaku.
パスワードを入力してこちらのケータイサイトから応募してほしい
I have to trust Suzaku.
今から一時間限定の受付だ
THE TASTE OF HUMILIATION
もちろん　特製待受けもあるぞ
それでは諸君　来週もお楽しみに